Greg Schomburg gschomburg@gmail.com gregschomburg.com 612 423 2883 184 Kosciuszko street apt 1 Brooklyn NY, 11216

I am a creative coder with a background in art and design. Over the course of my 15 year career, I have had the opportunity to work with a wide range of technologies, languages, and frameworks. My current focus is Unity and C# development for interactive installations and virtual reality experiences.

Career

Brand New School

http://brandnewschool.com

Role Senior Interactive Developer

2010 to 2017

Interaction Design and Development on a variety of interactive projects ranging from microsites and mobile apps to an 80 foot long multi-touchscreen installation.

Heavily involved in all interactive pitches including, technical research, concept development and proof-of-concept prototyping.

Oversaw technical coordination of freelance developer work, including defining tasks and daily check-ins.

Lead developer on a custom multi-Kinect-based body and gesture tracking system used for a large scale installation at the Chicago-O'hare airport.

Built http://brandnewschool.com, including custom CMS based on Expression Engine.

The Studio for Interactive Media

http://tsfim.com

Role Senior Interaction Designer

2007 to 2010

Worked as part of a small team creating boutique interactive installations for clients ranging from local nonprofits to Fortune 500 companies.

Worked on projects through entire lifecycle, from pitching to on-site installation.

Built front end for custom multi-room presentation system for Coca-Cola Innovation Lab installed in corporate headquarters in Atlanta and Shanghai.

Worked on internal research projects including IR motion tracking, FTIR touch screens, chatbots, and electronic prototyping.

Ham In The Fridge

http://haminthefridge.com

Role Designer / Developer

2005 to 2007

Worked with illustrators and animators to design and develop Flash games and seasonal activities for Cartoon Network.

Developed Flash minisites, games, and ad campaigns for Target.

Technologies & Languages

Extensive experience designing user experiences for a variety of platforms including: Large-scale digital installations, single- and multi-touch screen application, websites, mobile apps, AR and VR.

Extensive experience developing front-end experiences in a variety of languages, environments, and platforms including: Unity, C#, Objective-C, Javascript, Node, PHP, OpenFrameworks, Processing, Flash, Actionscript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, iOS, Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, VR, Hololens, AR, Arduino

Education

Minneapolis College of Art and Design BFA in Interactive Media 2002 to 2006